--==本字幕由 新浪微博@纸巾老湿eric 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩字幕 请关注 新浪微博@纸巾老湿eric
金属在咆哮...
Metal screams...
有东西正中我的胸膛...
something hits me square in the chest...
一阵天旋地转...
there's no up or down...
感觉自己飘在空中...
I don't weigh a thing...
我什么也不记得了
I don't remember a thing.
这看起来很不妙
This doesn't look good at all,
我一定又惹了什么事儿
I've gotta done something again.
真希望我能记起来
Wish I could remember what.
我是怎么到这里来的
How did I get here,
我做了些什么
what have I done,
为什么这么做
and why.
我一定是忘了吃药了
I must have forgotten my medicine.
我身体不太好
I've got a condition.
忘记吃药是一件很槽糕的事
It's bad to forget your medicine
尤其是身体不好的时候
when you got a condition.
肩上有子弹的擦伤
Covers up with bullets,
伤口还很新
the wound is fresh.
可能是一小时前的事
Maybe an hour old?
我不记得怎么受伤的了
I can't remember how I got it.
我还杀了人
And a live on me,
我记不起来了
I can't remember.
这片贫民区
The Projects...
一如寻常的丑陋
ugly as ever.
我他妈到底在这里干什么
What the hell am I doing here?
拼起记忆碎片
Put the pieces together.
好好想想
Remember.
现在是周六...
It's Saturday...
所以我肯定是在凯蒂的酒馆开始夜生活的
so I must have started the night at Kadie's joint.
一个和往常一样的周六夜晚
Just another Saturday night.
和其他所有废柴一样
Being all the other losers like me,
喝着小酒
sucking back the sauce,
像傻子一样对着南希流口水
drooling like fools over Nancy.
我当时心情不好
I wasn't in the mood,
看南希表演也没能让我高兴起来
even watching Nancy couldn't cheer me up.
我经常这么生气
I get that wrath sometimes.
没吃东西
Empty in the gut,
找不到女人
hollow in that lonely place
渴望找个理由打烂某人的脸
and wishing I had an excuse to break somebody's face.
就是个普通的周六夜晚
It was just another Saturday night.
我正在想该拿自己怎么办
I was wondering what I was gonna do with myself,
然后我闻到了一股难闻的气味
when I smelled something awful.
烧焦的毛发
Burning hair.
烧焦的肉
Burning meat.
好像这可怜的老家伙还不够惨似的
Like this poor old manos didn't have it bad enough already.
该死的兄弟会小子
Damn frat' boys!
被惯坏了的纨绔子弟
Damn rich spoiled brats!
别去烦他
Leave him be.
爬回去喝你的酒吧  贝尔尼尼男
Crawl back into your bottle, Bernini boy!
他为什么叫我"伯尼"
Why did he call me "Bernie"?
至少我知道他们是坏人了
At least I know they're bad guys.
杀几个这种人没什么错
Nothing wrong with killing a bunch of them.
操  这简直是我的公民义务
Hell, it's practically my civic duty.
这些蛀虫似的小白痴
Oh, these wormy little twits.
我讨厌这些人
I hate these guys.
求你了  杀了我吧
God just kill me, please.
他们逃之夭夭了
They made a run for it.
我做了每一个好市民都会做的事
I did what any good citizen would do.
去死吧
Go to hell!
怎么回事
What the hell!
这他妈什么情况
搞什么啊
What the hell!
我就是那时想到这个主意的
That's when I get my idea.
要是他们逃回了橡树区的大学
If they got back to the university at Sacred Oaks
我就再也抓不到他们了
I'd never catch them.
我追着他们满地跑
I bang them around like a hockey puck,
在拐弯时拦住他们
cut them off at every turn.
我让他们别无选择  只能冲过山头
I left them no choice but to head over the hill,
开进贫民区
to The Project.
我就可以转身离开
I could just turn my back
把他们留在那里
and leave them here.
我的老邻居们会帮我好好招待他们
My old neighbors will take care of them about good.
不过去他的
But hell,
我也要玩个痛快
why should they have all the fun!
贫民区
The Projects.
我是在这里出生的
I was born here.
我的老住处
My old neighborhood.
操  他死定了
Damn, he's a dead man!
我告诉你  我要好好开上一枪
I'm telling you, I want beat you a good shot.
他死定了
And he's a dead man!
我的老邻居们
My old neighbors.
他们让我明白他们正看着这一切
They let me know they're watching.
我提醒他们我的身份
I remind them who I'm.
并指示他们该做些什么
I tell them what to do.
不  不要  求求你
No, no please.
求求你了  我有钱
Please, I got money.
我有信托基金  我能付你钱
I got a trust fund, I can pay.
你是会付出代价的
You'll pay.
你开枪打我之前管我叫"伯尼"
Before you shot me, you called me "Bernie",
为什么叫我"伯尼"
why did you call me "Bernie"?
是贝尔尼尼  一个牌子
Bernini, is a brand name.
你穿的外套
That coat you're wearing,
就是贝尔尼尼的
it's a Bernini.
说明白了就好  小子
Thanks for clearing that up, kid.
刀
Knife!
贝尔尼尼是吧
Bernini, huh?
就是这件不错的外套
That one fine coat it is.
是谁花好多钱买来的吧
Somebody must have spent a fortune on it.
我想知道是谁
I wonder who.
想到这个
And while I'm at it,
我他妈是从哪搞来这副手套的
where the heck did I get these gloves?
我怎么也想不起来了
I can't remember for the life of me.
罪恶之城
蛇蝎美人
扑克牌
Poker...
在绅士手里
savage power...
也可以极具破坏力
in gentleman's hands.
是个好游戏
It's a good game!
好了
Now,
谁想玩
who wants to play?
去罪恶之城一定要提高警惕
Sin City is where you go in with your eyes open
否则就出不来了
or you don't come out at all.
但这城市就像个美女或赌场
But the city is like a woman or a casino.
总有人会赢
Somebody's gonna win
而我就是那个人
and it's gonna be me.
这种地方父亲不愿跟你说
It's the kind of place your father doesn't want to talk about.
但在我的家乡
But where I come from...
父亲貌似是种不存在的东西
father is a thing no one seems to be able to find.
罪恶之城
凯蒂俱乐部
我感觉运气不错
I was feeling lucky.
我在全城的酒馆里都赢了钱
I won money in joints all over the town.
最后终于来到了凯蒂
And I finally made it to Kadie's,
这里才真有挑战性
where the real score is.
这么不接着表演了
What happened to the show?
手气怎么样  陌生人
How's trick, stranger?
-正面还是反面  -正面
- Head or tail? - Head.
这才叫手气
That's a trick.
靠这个又赢不了钱
That won't get you anywhere.
跟着闪光的东西走
Follow the shiny object.
你是从哪儿来的  帅哥
Where'd you come from, handsome?
帮我个忙  朝这个吹口气
Do me a favor, blow in this.
这位幸运女士有名字吗
Does lady luck has a name?
玛茜
Marcie.
运气真好啊
Lucky man!
每次都是如此  夫人
Every time, ma'am.
真正的赌桌在哪
And where's the real lies?
宝贝儿  你不会想知道的
Baby, you don't want to know.
我还真想知道
I do want to know.
随你的便吧
Whatever you say, boss.
在吧台后面
Back at the bar,
你会死在那的
it's your funeral.
他会把你生吞活剥了
He'll eat you alive back there.
当心硌了牙
I'm pretty tough to chew.
走吧
Come on.
这次亲它一口
Kiss it this time.
-玛茜  -怎么了
- Hey Marcie, - Yeah?
你想赚点大钱吗
you want to go make some real money?
想啊
Yeah.
看牌
I'll check.
我叫一百
I bid a hundred.
晚上好
Goodnight.
我跟
I'll play.
我弃牌
I'll fold.
这个油头滑脑的是谁
Who is the slicker?
他在乔茜那被我抓过一次
I busted this one for craps over Jossie once.
继续玩  没事的
Play on, it's okay.
不管你怎么玩  小子  别赢得太狠了
Whatever you do, kid, don't win too much.
我从没输过
I never lose.
带美丽的女士来是什么意思
What's with bringing a fair lady over here?
她是我的幸运女神
That's my good-luck-charm.
再说了  我今晚已经大赢了一大笔
Besides I've had made a pretty nice dime tonight.
总得找个人把钱花出去啊  是吧
I gotta have someone to spend it on, right?
西尔维奥  让这位年轻的朋友来发牌吧
Silvio, let our young friend here do the honor, huh?
切牌
Cut.
新来的这孩子不错啊
New boy is good!
南希  南希  南希  南希
Nancy, Nancy, Nancy, Nancy!
南希  南希
Nancy, Nancy!
庄家拿两张牌
And the dealer will take two.
一百
One hundred.
我跟
I'll play.
我不玩了
I'm out.
我也不玩了
Yeah, me too.
-不跟  -我不玩了
- I'll fold. - I'm done.
傻眼了吧  小子
How dumb are you feeling now, boy?
是挺傻的
Pretty dumb.
参议员  我等着你下狠手呢
Oh senator, I'm ready for your worst.
小子  你还是别见识的好  哪怕是做梦
Boy, you don't even want to dream about my worst.
我从不做梦  只会实干
No, I don't imagine, I do.
所以我现在就要赢死你
That's why I'm gonna let you flatten your ass right now
然后回家
and call it a night.
当然  这是正直绅士之间公平的游戏
Sure, this is a fair game played by honorable man.
我加三百
I'm gonna raise you 300.
冷静点  小子
Easy, kid.
你到底知不知道自己招惹的是谁
You got any idea what you're up against?
在我看来我对面的是个男人
Looks to me like I'm up against a man.
你在招惹一个姓罗克的
You're up against a Roark.
我是在这里出生的  参议员
Yea, I was born here, senator.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我们迟早都会在这里死去
We all die here sooner or later.
我再加注五百
I'm gonna raise you another 500.
我喜欢这孩子
I like this kid.
我很喜欢他
I like him a lot!
我跟
I'm gonna call you.
反正你也不需要打车钱  是吧
You won't be needing anything for cab fare, will you?
你这手牌可真是好啊  朋友
Now that's the finest hand you ever gonna have, friend.
你可记住了手是什么做的
You just keep in mind what hands are made out of this.
我会的
Will do.
快滚  逃命去吧
Get your ass outta here, run like hell,
说不定还有点机会
you might still have a chance.
不行  我不能错过明晚的牌局
No, I can't miss tomorrow night's game,
就和你一样  长官
not any more than you can, officer.
而且  我已经答应了玛茜不会跑的
Besides, I already promised Marcie I don't turn.
我保护不了你的
I can't protect you.
那你还当什么警察
Then why you a cop?
我们要去哪里  强尼
Where are we going, Johnny?
哪里都去
Everywhere.
总有一天她会扣下扳机
One of these days she'll pull the trigger
到那时我就无能为力了
and then there's nothing I can do.
现在我也做不了什么
There's nothing I can do now.
我能做的只有求她...
All I can do is ask...
听着  不要
Listen, don't,
不要为我报仇  南希
don't avenge me, Nancy.
那会害死你的
It'll be the death of you.
而我无能为力
And I can't help.
我不忍再看了
I can't watch.
在罪恶之城  死亡和生存无异
Death is just like life in Sin City.
你什么也做不了
There's nothing you can do
而"爱"什么也战胜不了
and love doesn't conquer anything at all.
祝你好运  南希
Good luck, Nancy.
好好生活
Live well your life.
加油  甜心
Just try, sweetheart.
我们创造了罪恶之城的历史
We made Sin City history.
逛了城里的每个景点
Hit every hot spot in town.
赌桌上赢来的钱基本都花光了
I blow thru' almost as much cash as I made at the table.
我想用信用卡时  麻烦开始了
The trouble starts when I try to use my credit cards.
我相信一定是出了什么问题
I'm sure there must be some mistake.
我们很乐意为您提高额度
We'll be happy to extend you a line of credit.
怎么可能所有卡片在同一晚都被冻结了
How could all of them go bad in the same night?
你又不是没现金了
It's not like you don't have cash.
这不是重点  走吧
That's not the point, come on.
得送你回家了
We gotta get you home.
有什么东西跟着我们
Something comes up behind us.
一切都不对劲了
It smells all wrong.
这会拖慢我们的
This will slow us down.
你躲到一边去  玛茜
You get to the side, Marcie.
我得去修理几个人
I gotta break some bones.
你说什么呢  小傻子
What are you talking about, you silly.
你待在这儿就好
You just stay right there.
先生们  听着  我想我知道这是怎么回事
Gentleman, listen. I think I know what this is about,
我希望你们明白  我是不会反抗的
I want you to know you'd have no resistance from me
你手上拿着的那根短木棒
and that black jack you got in your hand
都能敲碎别人的脑壳了
could split somebody's skull open.
这都是怎么回事啊
What the hell was that all about?
你别管这事了
You stay out of sight now,
你在老城会很安全
and you'd be safe in old town.
去三床酒店跟我汇合
Meet me at the 3 Sheets Hotel.
166号房
Room 166.
6...什么
6...what?
咱们把这事了了吧
Let's get this over with.
我玩得太忘形了  是吧
I'm enjoying it too much, wasn't I?
你让我出丑了  孩子
You made a fool of me, boy.
在不该看我出丑的人面前
Right in front of the wrong people.
所有人的机会都是平等的  而你输了
You took your chance like we all did and you lost!
你知道我弄死像你这样的小杂碎有多容易吗
You have any idea how easy I kill little snots like you.
好了  来看看这只胜利之手吧
Now, let's see about that winning hand.
权贵们都看见那张牌桌上发生什么了
Powerful men watched what happened at that table.
我得让他们知道挑衅的代价
I need them to know the price of defiance.
权力是一种...很脆弱的东西
Power is a...fragile thing.
它不容任何威胁
It tolerates no threat.
挑衅者必须以身示范挑衅的代价
Defiance must be met with an example of the wages of defiance.
你最好现在就把我杀了
You'd be smart to kill me now.
我会让你比死还痛苦  小子
I'll do far worse than kill you, boy
小子  你遇上的
What you've encountered, boy,
可是权力
is power.
每当湿冷的风吹起
Everytime the wind blows cold and wet the thing
你的手和腿就会让你痛苦不已
that was your hand and your two legs and throw you in agony.
只要一下雨  你就会想起我
Whenever it rains, you'll remember me.
你永远会记住我的
You'll remember me, all the time,
我的儿子
my son.
没错  我知道你是谁
Oh yeah, I know who you are.
我一见到你就知道你是我的种了
I know you're one of mine the minute I saw you.
你有我们家族的影子  小子
Family resemblance, my boy.
可我他妈不在乎
But I don't give a damn.
我只有一个真正的儿子
I only have one real son,
伊森  愿他安息
Ethan, may he rest in peace..
他本可能当上总统的
He could be the president.
你真以为...
Do you really think...
我会认你吗
that I was going to claim you?
他狠狠揍了我一顿
He beat me rogue,
但等我回来
but when I get back,
规则就该变了
it'll be a whole different game.
又是一个炎热的夜晚
It's another hot night.
干燥无风
Dry and windless,
会让人做些容易出汗的
the kind that makes people do sweaty,
秘密的事
secret things,
一些能让我赚钱的事
things worth money to me.
这是最后一次了  萨莉
This is the last time, Sally.
这必须是最后一次了
This gotta be the last time.
你总是这么说
You always say that.
这次我是认真的
I mean it this time!
她从外套中缓缓滑出
She glides out of her coat
像在打开圣诞礼物的包装纸
like it is a Christmas wrapping,
竭尽所能地搔首弄姿
playing it for all it's worth
这可值不少钱
and it's worth plenty.
我们结束了
This is the end for us.
结束
The end for us?
因为我老婆
It's my wife.
她不停地问东问西  她起疑了
She's asking all kinds of questions. She suspects something.
她会去告我  然后得到一切
She'll sue and she'll get everything.
一切
Everything!
你努力赚来的一切
Everything you've worked so hard for.
我拼死拼活地工作
I worked my butt off.
我白手起家开创了自己的事业
I built my business up out of nothing.
白手起家
Nothing.
却没人懂得感激你  对吗  乔伊
Nobody appreciates you, do they, Joey?
起码不是以你应得的方式
Not the way you deserve.
的确没有
Nobody.
靠我养家糊口的员工不感激我
Not employees would be out on the street if it wasn't for me.
我从街上捡回来的妻子也不感激我
Not my wife who I found on the street!
你给她那么多珠宝  还有豪宅
The jewels and mansion you bought her.
还有我给她买的那些衣服
Wearing all those clothes that I got her!
花的都是我的钱  我辛辛苦苦赚来的钱
With my money! My hard-earned money!
我觉得你好厉害
I think you're so strong.
这你还真他妈说对了
You're damn right about that.
我得到任何回报了吗
Do I get any credit?
他们只会索取  索取  索取
They just take and take and take!
总有一天我把他们全开除了
One of these days I'm gonna fire the whole pack of them.
我要让他们看看谁才是老大
I'm gonna show them who's boss!
让我看看吧  乔伊
Show me, Joey.
让我看看谁是老大
Show me who's boss.
没错  我要让你看看  我要让你看看
Yeah, I'll show you, I'll show you.
我要让你看看谁是老大
I'll show you who's boss.
于是  她开始呻吟
Then she's moaning.
并随着他的抽插一遍遍喊着"老大"
And saying "boss" the same time with his movements.
很快就结束了
It's all over pretty quickly.
我得到了我需要的一切
I get everything I need.
真可惜  有些图片拍得还真不错
The sad thing is some of the composition is pretty good.
你让我体验到了做女人的快感
You make me feel like a woman.
我知道这听起来很老套但是真的
I know it sounds corny but it's true.
我爱你  宝贝
I love you, baby.
你知道我是爱你的
You know I love you
即便你是在骗我
even when you lie to me.
我的手腕好疼  乔伊
My wrist hurts, Joey.
你可以去把钥匙拿来了  就在我的包里
You can go get the key, it's just in my purse.
你完全不知道我牺牲了多少
You don't have any idea how much I sacrificed.
你在干什么  乔伊
What are you doing, Joey?
我对你的爱和我必须要做的事
It's tearing me up how much I love you,
让我痛不欲生
and what I gotta do.
可我工作得太辛苦了
But I worked too hard,
而洛莉将夺走一切
and Lori will get eveything
我不能让这种事发生
and I can't let that happen.
我别无选择  这都是她的错
I don't have any choice. It's all her fault.
乔伊  别这样
Joey, please...
我不会说出去的  我发誓
I won't tell anyone, I swear.
我知道你不会主动去说
I know you don't wanna talk.
我知道
I know that
但你也只是个普通人
but you're only human.
洛莉一定会发现你的存在
Lori is gonna find out about you,
就算她现在还不知道
if she doesn't know already.
然后她会给你一大笔钱
And she's gonna offer you a lot of money,
都是我的钱
my money.
她会用来买通你  然后整死我
She's gonna give it to you to bring me down!
-我会离开的  -那谁给你路费
- I'll go away! - Who's gonna pay for the ticket?
不只路费  鬼知道你还会要些什么
The ticket and God knows what else!
豪宅  名牌  还有豪车
Then the apartment, the clothes, the car.
你会张着血盆大口
You're gonna suck me dry
一步步把我榨干至死
and you'll never, ever stop!
不会的  求求你住手
No, please no!
打死他  打死他
Kill him! Kill him!
只要我在场
Nobody is killing anybody,
就不可以杀人
not while I'm around.
那搭个车总行吧
Then can I have a ride?
我取出钥匙  帮她解开了手铐
I grab the key and uncuff her.
她给了他一记"再见"
She gives him a goodbye that
让他每每想起都会隐隐作痛
will still hurt like hell when he comes to.
我把这小子拷在了床尾
I leave the slob handcuffed to the bed
以便服务生能发现他
for housekeeping to find.
我带着她翻山越岭  一路驶向了老城
I take her down over the hill toward old town.
谢谢你英雄救美
Thanks for my life, man.
萨莉渐渐消失在老城的人群中
Sally blends into the sea of flesh that is old town.
一切都回来了
They all come back.
那些关于老城的记忆
The damn old town memories,
烂醉的清晨  纵欲的夜晚
drunken mornings and sweaty sex
还有可笑至极的斗殴
and stupid bloody brawls.
还有刚才的事
and that thing I did.
生活不是简单的二选一
You can't just pick and choose.
不能一味只选好的而避开坏的
You can't take the good without the bad,
一旦释放心魔  就要承受恶果
not once you let the monster out.
我不能放它出来
I can't let it out.
不能再犯了
Never again.
我把车开到了十个街区以外
I drive 10 blocks out of my way
还象征性地给车加了点油
and stop for gas I don't need,
以免引火烧身
avoiding the worst of this job.
我的雇主
My employer,
那人的妻子
the wife.
她雇了律师处理财务事宜  一切都很顺利
This one has got a lawyer to pay the tab, so it's easier.
离开时请走员工出口
Please leave by the servant's exit.
野马车低声咆哮着
The mustang shudders,
渴望化身为脱缰的野马自由驰骋
begging to cut loose and show what it can do.
它想带我一同飞奔
It wants to take me all the way.
可我不让
I don't let it.
我想着曾经搞砸的一切
I think about all the ways I've screwed up
想着怎样才能有机会洗心革面
and what I'd give for one clear chance to wipe this slate clean.
我愿付出任何代价  只为挣脱束缚
I'd give anything, just to cut loose,
只为再一次
just to feel the fire...
感受那种激情
one more time.
决不能失控
Never lose control,
一秒也不行
not for a second.
绝不能让心魔吞噬自己
Never let the monster out.
勿忘彼时
Remember when you did.
勿忘彼事
Remember what you did.
找谁
Yeah?
德怀特  是你吗
Dwight, is that you?
艾娃
Ava.
很抱歉打给你
I'm sorry to call.
我知道我没这个权力
I know I've got no right
可我真的需要见你
but I need to see you,
就今晚
tonight.
求你了  德怀特  别挂  好吗
Please Dwight, don't hang up, please.
她就这么一直说着
She keeps talking.
我杵在那儿  傻瓜一样地听着
Like an idiot, I keep listening.
艾娃
Ava.
该死
Damn.
我真该叫她去见鬼的
I should tell her to go to hell.
相反  我却早到了20分钟
Instead, I show up 20 minutes early.
她现在又在打我什么主意
What the hell she wants with me now?
在罪恶之城里
You can't drive 2 blocks
每隔两个街区就有一家"沙龙"
in Sin City without coming across a salon.
寻欢作乐的那种
The bad kind.
为什么选这里  艾娃
Why here, Ava?
你不是什么东西都得要最好的吗
With you everything always had to be first class.
每当我没钱付账时
And when I couldn't foot the bill,
你总能另找一个付得起钱的主
you sure as hell found somebody who could.
我叫了杯姜汁啤酒
I ordered up a ginger ale and
对着门口盯了将近半小时
stared at it for the better half part of an hour.
她迟到了
She is late,
一如既往
like she always was,
可也一如既往
and like always,
她值得让人等
she is worth the wait..
德怀特
Dwight.
我们有多久没见了
How long has it been?
四年了吧
4 years?
是啊  差不多吧
Yeah, that sounds about right.
坐下吧
Have a seat.
多少次我拿起电话又放下
So many times I wanted to call you.
脑子里想的都是你
I found myself thinking about you.
-一直都是  -我还有事
- Constantly. -I got places to go,
还是有话直说吧
how about you tell me what you want.
别这么冷淡
Don't be cold.
我可能承受不了
I don't think I could stand that right now.
你一定还惦记着我吧
I must still mean something to you.
你来了  说明你还在乎我
You came here, you must have cared.
是啊
Sure.
电话一挂我就飞奔过来
You called and I came running.
你还是让我无法抵抗  也许永远抵抗不了
You still got that much of a hold on me, maybe you always will,
但这不代表我会给你好脸色看
but I got no reason at all to be nice to you.
算我活该吧
I guess I deserve that.
咱们就别兜圈子了
Let's not screw around.
我已经来了
I'm here.
洗耳恭听
I'm listening.
告诉我你到底想怎样
Just tell me what the hell it is you want?
我只想求你一件事
There's only one thing I want from you,
是让我梦寐以求  甚至为之疯狂的
I want it so desperately that I could scream.
我想乞求你的原谅
I want you to forgive me.
看来你还是有良心的啊
So you got a conscience after all.
好吧
Fine.
如你所愿  我原谅你
I forgive you, you got your wish.
你可以回家
Now go home,
安心睡个好觉了
sleep tight.
你之前说得对
You're right about me.
我是个自私的婊子  抛弃了唯一的挚爱
I'm a selfish slut who threw away the only man she ever loved.
可我知道错了
But I was wrong.
说得真好听
Good one.
只可惜我早不是三岁小孩子了
I was born at night but it wasn't last night.
我过得很煎熬  德怀特
I'm in hell, Dwight.
煎熬得你无法想象
It's worse than you can imagine.
自作孽不可活
You made your bed, sleep in it!
-亲爱的  求你了  原谅我吧  -少来
- Forgive me, darling, I beg you. - No!
-我爱你  -不行
- I love you. - No!
不行
No!
你再这样  我发誓会杀了你
You do that again, I swear to hell I'll kill you.
如果真的无法原谅我
If you can't forgive me,
那请你永远记住我吧
then please remember me.
据说只要有人惦记  你就不会真正死去
They say you never die as long as somebody remembers you.
你又在鬼扯些什么
What the devil are you talking about?
洛德夫人
Mrs. Lord.
天气回凉了  这附近治安也不好
The weather is inclement, the neighbourhood is bad
而且您身边这位...
and your present company...
很掉档次
is low.
您该回家了  洛德夫人
You're due at home, Mrs. Lord.
她回不回家你管不着
I'd say that's up to Mrs. Lord.
这事和你没关系  先生
This is none of your concern, sir.
我们之间要是发生肢体冲突
Any physical contest between us
只会有一种结果
has only one outcome.
我说老兄
Hey buddy,
那蠢蛋在为难你吗
is that dickhead giving you a hard time?
要不要我帮你扁他
You want me to break him down for you?
反正我今晚闲得手痒痒
I got nothing going on tonight.
他上的话  那还真是场好戏了
That would be an interesting contest.
不关他的事
It's not his fight.
没事的  德怀特  反正也晚了
Never mind, Dwight, it's too late.
我跟他走就是了
I'll go with him.
什么晚了  艾娃
Too late for what, Ava?
一切
For everything.
请一定要记住我  亲爱的
Just remember me, my love.
记住我
Remember me.
今晚您可有得忙了  洛德夫人
You'll have business tonight, Mrs. Lord,
一些不愉快的事
Unpleasant business.
我已经不在乎了
I don't care anymore.
那时的温度没有下降
The night air hasn't got any colder,
是我的心凉了
it just feels that way.
老兄  我也不想
Buddy, I don't mean to
对你们的私事指手画脚的  不过...
poke my nose right where it don't belong but...
小心红颜祸水啊
that there, is a dame to kill for.
艾娃...可恶
Ava...damn!
日出又日落  一天就这么过去了
Night turns to day and then it's night again
我无法逃避自己的内心
and there's no where to hide.
她根本不值得丝毫的想念
She isn't worth a moment's thought
可我却无法将她从我脑中抹去
and I can't get her out of my head.
我怎么开始抽烟了
What am I doing smoking?
这香烟又是哪儿来的
Where did I get these cigarettes?
是艾娃让你心烦意乱
It's Ava making you crazy.
一切如昨
All over again.
千万别让心魔吞噬自己
Never let the monster out.
忘了她
Shake her off.
不管发生什么  都是她自找的
Whatever she's in for, she deserves it,
可我必须了解事情的真相
but I have to know what's wrong.
到橡树区只有几小时车程
It's a couple hours of drive out to Sacred Oaks.
费不了多大劲就能弄清真相了
It shouldn't take too much effort to get to the bottom of this.
只是简单地私闯民宅
Just a simple job of breaking and entering,
不杀人的话
punishable by up to 5 years
顶多在监狱蹲上五年
in the slammer even if I don't kill anybody.
可这次所见却是我万万没想到的
I wind up seeing a lot more than I bargained for.
她看起来毫发无损  悠然自得
She seems perfectly goddamn fine.
毫无家暴痕迹
Not roughed up,
只是个阔太太  正如她一直想要的
just the rich man's wife like she always intended to be.
我他妈就是个白痴
I'm a damn fool.
别动  偷窥狂
Freeze! Pervert!.
让我过去  马努特
Let me through, Manute.
对不起  德怀特
I'm sorry, Dwight.
这一脚简直让我痛不欲生
An atom bomb goes off between my legs.
而这几拳更像是撞上了万吨巨轮
A freight train barrows into my jaw.
我以前被打过不少次  可没遇过这么重的
I've taken a beating before but never like this.
从没遇过
Never like this.
耳边的声音愈发遥远
The sounds go wet.
可能他还没停手吧
Maybe he keeps hitting me.
我也不清楚...
I don't know...
我渐渐失去了知觉
...I'm gone.
像是去到了那个永无疼痛的极乐世界
Gone to that place where there's no pain or thought.
我在半空中醒来
I wake up in mid air.
坚硬的路面狠狠赏了我一个吻
The pavement rushes up to give me a big sloppy kiss.
不会吧
I'll be damned.
这都送到家门口了
Door to door service.
我发现了我的野马车
Then I spot my Mustang,
没理由啊
which makes no sense.
他们怎么会把我的车还回来
Why would they return my car?
滚出去
Get out of here.
不
No.
穿上衣服  立马给我走人
Put your clothes back on and get out of here, now!
不
No.
你本可以置之不理的
You had your chance.
可你终究还是来找我了
You could've stay away but you came for me.
你心里还有我
You still want me,
现在我是你的了
and I'm yours, now!
今晚
Tonight!
滚出我的世界  永远别回来
Get out of my life once and for all
否则我会揍得你满地找牙
or I'll bash your teeth in.
如果你无法爱我
If you can't love me,
那就恨我吧
hate me.
如果你无法原谅我
If you can't forgive me,
那就惩罚我吧
punish me.
伤害我  就像我伤害你那样
Make me hurt, like I've hurt you.
我用各种肮脏的话语骂她
I called her every foul name there is.
可我的名字在她嘴里却无比美妙
She makes my name sound like music,
如同唱给恶灵的颂诗
like a chant to some dark god.
她香汗淋漓  楚楚动人
She's slippery with sweat.
不久  我的仇恨便烟消云散了
Before long, my hatred is spent.
可她还不罢休
But she won't let go.
她吻着我  哄着我
She kisses me and coaxes me
情欲的烈火再度蔓延
and the fire grows again.
我说了些我发誓不再说的话
I said all the thing I swore I'd never say again.
我是她的
She owns me.
肉体和灵魂
Body and soul.
把一切都告诉我
Tell me everything.
马努特  揍你的那个人
Manute, the man who beat you.
他是个施暴的专家
He's a specialist inflicting pain.
蹂躏过刚才你让我无比愉悦的每寸肌肤
Hideous pain in all the places you just gave me joy.
真恶心  他疯了吧
That's sick, it's crazy.
达米安  我的丈夫
Damien, my husband,
只会说着风凉话袖手旁观
he talks and talks and watches.
一次比一次糟糕
It's worse each time.
这能让他得到他要的变态高潮
It's getting closer to his final sick climax.
他还说会让我死得很难看
He says it'll be very ugly before I die.
你不会死的  艾娃
Ava, you're not gonna die.
我会保护你的
You're coming with me.
算了吧
It's hopeless.
我想跑他都不会拦我  甚至还嘲笑我
He lets me run away, even laughs about it.
我去哪儿  干什么  他都不管
Doesn't care where I go, what I do.
他知道马努特总能找到我
He knows Manute will always find me.
我说得对吗  马努特
Isn't that right, Manute?
夫人  洛德先生希望你能自重
Ma'am, Mr Lord would require that you be disciplined.
不  德怀特  别跟他动手
No, wait, Dwight, don't fight him!
他会要了你的命
He will kill you!
他可不是一般人
He's not human.
我用尽力气揍他  可他纹丝不动
I punch with all door, he doesn't fall down.
于是我又补了一拳
So I punched him again.
一记千斤重拳砸在了我的胸口
A wrecking ball hits me square in the chest.
洛德夫人  披上衣服
Mrs. Lord, your clothes.
我们还有事要做呢
We have an appointment.
他们休想从我身边夺走她
They can't take her away from me.
这次不行
Not this time.
我很清楚该怎么做
I know exactly what to do.
我很清楚该去哪
I know exactly where to go.
酒吧里有个备受保护的女孩
Now here's a girl with protection.
虽然平日会在那些淫荡醉鬼面前
She maybe showing off everything she has got
竭尽全力搔首弄姿
and already die full of horny drunks,
不过南希现在是最可靠的美人了
but Nancy is the safest gal in the world.
敢碰南希一下
Make a grab for Nancy
你要迎接的就是300磅的铁拳了
and you're up against 300 pounds of iron
把你撂倒的那个人...
that goes by the name of...
叫马维
...Marv.
马维
Marv.
德怀特  真高兴在这儿见到你
Dwight, mighty glad to see you here.
需要我做什么吗
What can I do you for?
帮我个忙
I need your help.
这事儿挺麻烦的  弄不好会吃些子弹
It's bad and it's gonna be up against a lot of guns.
算我一个
Count me in.
我正好换换口味
I could use a change of peace.
我们喝了个底朝天
We finished off the bottle,
让这流动的黑暗填满了内心
letting this liquid darkness fill us both.
当我确定他已喝足了酒
When I'm sure he had enough
绝对招惹不得的时候
to make him good and dangerous,
我告诉了他艾娃的事
I tell him about Ava
他血红的双眼弥漫着杀气
and his eyes go killer red.
我知道他会为我拼上性命
I know he's willing to die for me
如有必要的话
if that's what it takes.
我的确是在利用他  那又怎样
So I'm using him, so what?
他现在打的是我想打的人
So he breaks the faces I want him to break
而不是其他人
instead of somebody else's.
他能让艾娃重回我的怀抱
So he helps me get Ava back in my arms again
而不是困在那破房子里生不如死
instead of sleeping it off in a slum house or gutter.
反正他的命也不值几个钱
His life isn't worth a dime anyway.
就算我没让他送命  他也迟早会死
If I don't get him killed, the world will,
早晚的事
one way or another.
把枪留在车上
I want you to leave that thing in the car.
今晚不杀人
Nobody's getting killed tonight.
得了吧  德怀特  这样还有什么乐子
Oh come on Dwight, why, you're no fun at all.
翻过大门后  我们分头行动
We split up at the gate.
很快  马维就引起了他们的注意
It doesn't take Marv long to get their attention.
你擅闯了圣地
You've trespassed on hallowed ground.
就是你这个混球让我朋友难堪的吗
You're the slug that freaked my friend out?
开始吗
Shall we?
以后一定得把手包起来
Oh, I better wrap my hand one of these days.
艾娃的事我一定会调查清楚
I'll find the truth about Ava,
也不知道她现在怎么样了
and what's happening to her now.
那人知道真相  我得让他说出实话
He will tell me. I'll get it out of him.
达米安·洛德
Damien Lord.
她在哪儿
Where's she?
你把她怎么了
What have you done with her?
你是过来救她于水火的吗
Have you come to take her away from all these?
这次的故事又有什么狗血桥段
And what's all these in her present story?
我不清楚她到底和你瞎掰了些什么
I haven't the slightest notion what nonsense my wife has told you
我也懒得关心
nor do I care.
反正都是编的
It's all lie.
离那桌子远点儿
Stay away from the desk.
那女人有病
The woman is pathological.
你被耍了
You have been deceived.
感觉怎么样
What did it feel like?
什么
What?
杀死一个无辜的人
Murdering an innocent man.
真想知道是什么感觉
I just want to know what it felt like.
一定美妙极了
It must've been beautiful.
你说什么  无辜
What are you talking about, innocence?
我就知道你靠得住
I knew I could count on you.
性爱总会让你犯蠢  轻易相信任何事
Sex always made you stupid, ready to believe anything.
你刚成就了我的富贵梦
You've just made me a very rich woman.
最后帮我个忙吧  亲爱的
Do me one last favor, lover.
站在那儿别动  好让我一枪崩了你的头
Stay still long enough for me to blow your brains out.
枪法我不在行
I'm not much of a shot
-可我会尽量  -艾娃
- but I'll do my best. - Ava...
我设了圈套  你就跳进来了
I planned it and you fell for it.
这将是我最后一次有求于男人
This is the last time I'm gonna need anything from a man.
最后一次出卖我的肉体
The last time I make my living on my back.
-马努特从没伤害过你  -他敢
- Manute never hurt you... - He wouldn't dare!
-你疯了  -不  德怀特
- You're insane. - No, Dwight.
相信我的人才疯了
A crazy person would be anyone who believes me
那就是你
and that would be you.
如果我现在吻你  德怀特
If I kiss you now, Dwight,
你会相信这是爱吗
would you still believe it was... love?
艾娃
Ava...
该死
Damn.
我按承诺把那个大块头搞定了
Hey, I handled that big slug just like I promised.
我没杀他  也没废了他
I didn't kill him, I didn't even cripple him.
也就卧床6个月吧  顶天了
6 months in contraption, that's all, tops.
不过我卸了他一只眼珠子
I took an eye out of him though.
听着  我先声明
Listen, before you say anything.
我知道我本该低调点跑路的
I know I was supposed to take this down to make my getaway
可当我看见这尤物停在那里  你懂的
but when I saw this beauty here sitting there, you know
钥匙插好了  可以直接开走
the key in the ignition and everything,
我可不能错过机会
I couldn't pass a chance to, uh,
咱俩一起开车爽一爽
take a drive and get us on this tucker.
靠边停车
Pull over!
这种车一共也没生产几辆
You know, they only made a couple of these beauties
我还看过一部有关它的电影
I saw a movie about it once.
我在这儿说了半天  你都快血流成河了
Oh, here I'm, jabbering and you're leaking all over the place.
我带你去我一朋友那儿
I'll get you to a guy I know.
他擅长处理枪伤  也不会问东问西
He's good with bullets and uh, he don't ask no questions.
带我去老城
Get me to old town.
伙计  我实话跟你说
Let me level with you, pal.
你撑不到老城的
You ain't gonna make it to old town.
我能坚持住
I'll make it.
我还有很多事未完之事  不能死
I got too much I got to do to let myself die.
去老城
old town.
他流了很多血  洛德夫人
He left a lot of blood, Mrs. Lord.
跑不了多远的
He won't get far.
你说你认识他
You said you knew him.
凶手叫德怀特
The killer's name is Dwight.
德怀特·麦卡锡
Dwight McCarthy.
你们是什么关系
You know him in what sense?
难以启齿的关系
Why, a depplicable one.
抱歉  警长  您对我这么耐心
I'm sorry, lieutenant. You've been so very patient with me.
你我虽然素未谋面
You and I barely met but already...
但我觉得我能信任您
I feel I can trust you.
你可以信任我
You can trust me.
几年前我们在一起过一段时间
We were together for a while a few years ago.
结果不是很好
It went badly.
他变得很不正常
He went insane.
开始自我幻想  并且胡乱指责我
He started imagining things, accusing me of things.
无论我去哪儿他都跟着我
He followed me wherever I went.
最近  他还擅自闯进这栋房子
Recently, he broke into this very property.
他打过你吗
Did he beat you?
喝醉的时候会
When he drank.
他是个酒鬼
He drank a lot.
那你还跟这个疯子在一起
You stayed with this nutcase?
你不用理会他
Never mind that.
女人的容忍度超乎你的想象
You'll be surprise how much a woman can take.
你吓坏了
You were terrified.
是达米安给了我新生
It was Damien who took me away.
他是那么体贴  那么可靠
He was so...gentle and sure.
我想我是个需要保护的女人
I suppose I'm a woman who needs...protection.
他让我很有安全感
He made me feel safe
然而  德怀特  他最终还是找到了我
but then, Dwight, he found me somehow.
他在半夜给我打恐吓电话
He started calling me late at night, making awful threats.
现在达米安死了
And now Damien is dead
我孤身一人
and I'm alone.
请帮帮我  警长
Oh please, lieutenant.
叫我莫特吧
Call me Mort.
需要安慰的寡妇真是撩人
Nothing like a widow in need of confort.
光是看着就有点把持不住了
I got a stiffy just watching her.
-她真有韵味  -别说了  鲍勃
- Man, she's prime. - Just drop it, Bob.
这等大好机会岂能错过
You don't pass up a chance like that.
要是没有点好处
What's the point of being a Sin City cop
在罪恶之城当警察还有什么意思
if you don't get the perks?
我们是有妇之夫  鲍勃
We're married man, Bob.
我才不管你是什么
I don't care what you are.
看看那美人
Will you just take a look at that babe!
行了  鲍勃
That's enough, Bob.
情况不太妙
This doesn't look good.
有辆警车还在追我们
One squad car still chases us.
肯定是个新手
Must be a rookie driving.
那些哥们儿应该告诉他
His buddy should've told him
老城的姑娘们有自己的行事方法
the girls of old town have laws all their own,
她们对条子可不会手下留情
and they don't take kind to the cops.
瞧啊
Oh, look that.
姑娘们  你们太赞了
Oh, you're a genius, girl.
我们到了  伙计
Here we are, pal.
好像来这不怎么明智
Out of a sudden this doesn't look like the brightest idea you ever had.
给你10秒钟
You've 10 seconds to tell us
交代为什么把条子招来老城
what you're doing bringing cops to old town.
问题来了
Here's the problem.
我从不打女人
I don't fight girls.
盖尔
Gail!
-是我  -德怀特
- It's me. - Dwight.
他们对你做了什么
What have they done to you?
子弹正中胸口
The cork screw stamps me square in the chest
使我苦不堪言
and twists.
快去叫莫莉
Get Molly!
叫所有人都过来
Get everybody.
终于打来了
It's about time.
-喂  -洛德夫人
- Hello? - Mrs. Lord.
警长  莫特  你能来电话真是太好了
Lieutenant...Mort. You're so kind to call.
希望我没打搅你休息
I hope I didn't wake you.
没  我没睡觉  我完全睡不着
No, I wasn't sleeping. I haven't slept at all.
一想到他还逍遥法外
I'm jumping at every sound,
任何声响都让我坐立不安
just knowing he's still out there.
我想我还是不够坚强吧
I guess I'm not a very strong person.
而且又孤身一人在这空旷的房子里
And me in the house all alone.
别把自己逼这么紧  洛德夫人
You shouldn't be so hard on yourself, Mrs. Lord.
不安是正常的
You're having a very understandable reaction.
有什么我能为你做的吗
Is there any thing at all I can do for you?
我知道我这样很不好
I know it's a bad thing to think of you the way I do.
这会给你添麻烦
It's...inconvenient.
但是坠入爱河的人
But whoever loved,
又有谁不是一见钟情呢
love not at first sight?
我自见面后就对你无法忘怀
I thought about you since I saw you.
我现在就在想你
I'm thinking about you now.
你有想我吗
Were you thinking about me?
有
Yes.
我不想说出来
I hate myself for saying this but
但我觉得漫漫长夜一个人没法过
I just don't know if I could bear to be alone tonight.
我的心还在跳
My heart beats.
我闻到了煮咖啡的香味
I take in the rich burnt smell of coffee.
盖尔  她足以唤醒我了
Gail! She's reason enough to open my eyes.
能听见我说话吗  德怀特
Can you hear me, Dwight?
条子们正在找你  德怀特
The cops want you bad, Dwight.
情况很严峻
Really bad.
别担心
Don't worry.
我们会治好你的
We'll fix you up
到那时候
and when we do,
等你好了
when you're all better,
咱们再好好聊聊你当初一走了之的事
I'll dag you for leaving in the first place!
我说过  你总有一天会回来的
I told you, you would be back.
我告诉过你了
I told you.
你属于这里
You belong here.
混蛋
Jerk!
我以为外面还有另一个世界
I thought there's another world out there.
我以为我可以融进去
I thought I could be a part of it.
外面只有罪恶之城
There's only Sin City.
莫莉说你准备走了
Molly said you're ready to leave.
不  我要留下来
No, I'm staying.
回答错误
Wrong answer.
米霍
Miho.
致命的米霍
Deadly little Miho.
就算她认出我  也不会显露出来
If she recognizes me, she doesn't let it show.
你真是选错了藏身之处
Oh, you picked the wrong neighborhood for your hideout.
无论你是死是活  都必须得走
Alive or dead, you're leaving.
我要留在这儿
I'm staying.
我觉得他感觉不到  米霍
I don't think he can feel it, Miho.
把刀拧一拧
Give it a twist.
你别再说要留下来的话了
You won't give with anymore lip about staying here,
否则米霍就得把你...除掉
or Miho will have to...exhale.
而莫莉千辛万苦拯救回来的小心脏
And that heart Molly worked so hard to fix
也保不住了
will just pop like a grape.
他会留下
He's staying.
如果你们要杀了他
And if you're gonna kill him,
最好连我也一起杀了
you better kill me too,
虽然他没爱过我
eventhough he doesn't feel the same way about me.
但我只爱过他一个
He's the only man I ever loved.
大家似乎都在等其他人动作
They all seem to be waiting for the other shoe to drop,
盖尔先开口了
Gail drops it.
那晚路很黑  米霍
It was dark in that alley, Miho.
当时你15岁  你杀了三个暴徒
When you were 15, you killed three of the thugs.
但你身后还有两个
But the last two have a drop on you.
要不是有人出现
You were dead,
你已经死了
until someone appeared.
你没看清救你的人是谁
You never got a good look at the man who saved you.
现在仔细看看吧
Take a look now.
我得到了更多的时间
I get more time
以及更多的手术
and more surgery.
听着  只有一个人
Listen, there's only one person
能从达米安·洛德的死中获利
that has anything to gain for snuffimg Damien Lord
而你却在忙着跟她鬼混
and you're too busy banging the broth
妨碍审讯进程
to bring her in for questioning!
你不了解她
You don't know her.
你根本不了解她
You don't know anything about her and
你再这么说她
I'll be damned if I let you use that kind of language
我就不客气了
when you talk about her.
你爱上她了
You're in love with her!
你个蠢货
You stupid smug!
你跟她私下幽会是一回事
It's one thing to poke a babe on the side,
但你现在简直被迷昏了头
but you can't even think straight.
你他妈给我闭嘴
Shut the hell up!
我知道我在干什么
I know what I'm doing.
我本该把一切都告诉你的
I guess I should've told you everything.
没错  你应该说
You're damn right you should've.
他强奸了我
He raped me.
还差点杀了我
He almost killed me.
那个混蛋
That son of a bitch!
我以为我能跟他讲道理
I thought I could reason with him but
但他比以前更疯狂
he was worse than ever.
他的手掐着我的喉咙
His hands at my throat,
强奸我的时候一直掐着
strangling me while he did what he needed to do.
他会杀了我的  杀了我  杀了我
He will kill me, kill me, kill me...
我只有你了
I have only you.
我爱你  莫特
I love you, Mort.
保护我
Keep me safe.
保护我  保护我  保护我
Keep me, keep me, keep me...
艾娃·洛德
Ava Lord.
这次你没打中我的心
For once you missed my heart.
我恢复得很快  艾娃
I'm healing quickly, Ava.
我马上就能去找你算账了
I'll be coming for you soon.
你明知道他在哪却什么都不做
You know where he is and you won't do a damn thing about it!
你不知道这有多难
You don't know what you're asking.
我们得等老城的人把他放出来再说
We've to wait for old town to give him up,
这是唯一的办法
it's the only way.
你是罪恶之城的警察
You're a Sin City cop.
你拿着警徽配着枪  你有权力
You got a badge and a gun. You got power.
好好利用
Use it!
如果你还想要我
If you ever want to have this woman again,
那就像个男人  如果你是个男人
be a man. If you're a man...
杀了他
kill him!
别动
Don't move.
麦卡锡
McCarthy...
你没虐待过她
You never tortured her.
你俩合伙耍了我  你是她的情人
You two cooked that up. You were her lover.
你这个傻瓜
You were a fool.
女神没有情人
The goddess takes no lover.
男人只是她的奴隶
The goddess makes slave of man.
只需一瞬  她就能看透你的心
In an instant, she can see thru' the heart of you
然后把它转化成你内心最深处的渴望
and transformed to your deepest desire.
对达米安·洛德来说  她是美丽的新娘
To Damien Lord, she was the princess bride.
对你来说  她是患难的少女
To you, a damsel in distress.
她毁了你们所有人
She devoured all of you.
你们无法与女神对抗
You cannot defeat the goddess.
她永远都不会死
She cannot die.
你跟她一样不可理喻
You're as crazy as she is.
要是你也跟她一样烂
If you were as rotten as her,
我现在会一枪崩了你
I would blow your brains out right now,
但是我现在不轻易杀人
but I'm trying to be careful about who I kill
你之前也不过是揍了我一顿而已
and all you did was pound the crap out of me.
也已经付出一只眼睛的代价了
You already paid an eye for that.
我放你一马  但是警告你
I'm letting you go with a warning.
老实待在床上
Stay in bed.
别回去
Don't go back to work.
别挡我的道儿
And don't get in my way.
不  艾娃  你不是女神
No, Ava, you're no goddess.
你是个女巫
You're a witch.
一个掠食者
A predator.
也许我是罪有应得  但是其他人呢
Maybe I only got what I deserved but what about the others?
好人都变得丧心病狂了
Good man driven mad.
你真是丧失心智了
You really lost it.
你最好别为了那个婊子离开妻子
Bad enough you leave your wife for that skank.
注意你的用词  狗娘养的
You watch what you call her, you son of a bitch.
你放弃了你的事业
You throw it away your career.
现在又要去自杀  你个笨蛋
Now you commit suicide, you stupid shit!
我知道我在干什么  我要去老城
I know what I'm doing, I'm going to old town.
我要彻底了结这个男人
I'm going to nail this guy once and for all.
你不愿意来可以不来
If I had to go it alone, I'll.
就算我求你了
Do me a favor,
把车掉头  赶紧回警局去
turn the car around and you go back to the station.
跟局长讲清楚
You gotta complain with the captain.
我是个警察  在做自己的本职工作
I'm a cop. I'm doing my job.
去城里抓捕罪犯
I'm in town for a murder.
别再想那个贱人了
You gotta ditch that dame!
够了
That's enough!
不准你说艾娃
You won't talk about Ava!
有人会让你清醒的
Somebody's gonna set you straight.
你必须忘了那个臭婊子
You gotta forget about that stupid whore!
掉头  否则我将逮捕你
Turn the car around or I'm turning you in!
我警告过你
I warned you.
每天我都警告你  但你还是如此
Everyday, I warned you but you keep asking for it!
你要找死  那就成全你  伙计
You're asking for it! Well, here it's, pal!
莫特  不要
Mort, No!
一个女巫
A witch,
一个掠食者
a predator,
摧毁生灵
destroying lives.
有时为了权力
Sometimes for power,
有时为了利益
sometimes for profit,
有时  只是玩玩而已
sometimes...for sport.
但你现在被禁锢在这别墅里
But now you're locked away in your mansion.
如同笼子里请愿的小鸟
A bird of prey in a gilded cage.
准备好干蠢事了吗
Are you ready to do something stupid?
很高兴你光临我的聚会  沃伦奎斯特先生
I'm so happy you chose to attend my little party, Herr Wallenquist.
你的邀请让我很意外  洛德夫人
Your invitation surprised me, Mrs. Lord.
你的丈夫跟犯罪团伙毫无往来
Your husband had no criminal associations.
我真的调查过
Believe me, I tried.
我能说实话吗  沃伦奎斯特先生
May I speak truthfully, Mr. Wallenquist?
当然
Please.
老城是你的眼中钉
old town is a thorn in your sight.
确实如此
Indeed it is.
那群婊子坐收那么多钱
All those profits in the hands of whores.
你一定想好好管管她们吧
Surely you want to put them in their place.
稍做些调整  平衡一下权力
Make some adjustment to the balance of power.
让她们见识一下谁才是这里的老大
Show them who rules Sin City.
你的话对我不起作用  洛德夫人
You've limited influence on me, Mrs. Lord.
我有点生疏了
I haven't been doing so very badly.
那两个警察的事  还真是失策啊
But those two policeman, that was an embarassing blunder.
是的  我现在孤军奋战了
Yes, I'm out of my league.
我需要更强大  更有经验的帮手
I need a stronger, more experience hand.
我要整个洛德集团
I need all enterprises joined... in matrimony,
和专业而强硬的沃伦奎斯特集团联姻
with the expertise and iron fist of a rich Wallenquist.
你要的是德怀特·麦卡锡的尸体
What you need is the corpse of Dwight Mccarthy
和他承认谋杀达米安·洛德的一纸遗书
and a suicide note which he confesses to the murder of Damien Lord.
而你要让那些老城的贱人们知道谁才是老大
And you need to show those old town bitches who's boss.
的确如此
Indeed, I do.
德克萨斯有个专家
There's a specialist in Texas.
我可以安排他明天就乘火车来
I could have him on a train tomorrow.
我直接跟他讲
I'll brief him myself.
他在午夜会到你家
He will on your doorstep at midnight.
办成我就是你的人了
And I'll be yours forever.
为你的灵魂祈祷吧  艾娃
Pray for your soul, Ava.
他以后还会再来罪恶之城
This won't be his last to visit Sin City.
晚上好  克尔伐先生
Good evening, Mr. Kelvar.
-我帮您拿包  -别碰我的装备
- I'll take your bag. - Nobody touches my gear.
而且我有人来接
And I got somebody picking me up
可比你可爱多了
who's one hell of a lot cuter than you.
我们还以为您是一个人来的
It was our understanding that you're travelling alone.
我这个人充满了惊喜
I'm full of surprises.
去副驾驶的位子坐着
Shuffle that bootie over to that shotgun side now.
我来开车
I'm driving.
我跟着你的车
Follow you.
洛德夫人可能会不太高兴
Mrs. Lord may not be please.
是她找我办事
She's the one with the problem.
我随时可以走人
I can always get back on the train.
在这等我
Wait here.
快点回来
Hurry back!
你知道我会等不及的
You know I'll get impatient.
你也知道我等不及的时候就会做疯狂的事
You know I get a little crazy when I get impatient.
克鲁格  看好这个女人
Kruger, watch this woman.
雅各比
Jacoby,
如果他动一下  就杀了他
If this man moves, kill him.
我以为我们是要谈生意的
Thought this was business.
手术做得很好啊  麦卡锡先生
My compliments to your surgeon, Mr. McCarthy.
惊人的转变
Remarkable transformation...
但你的眼睛没变
which you still have the eyes,
还是死人的眼睛
the eyes of a dead man.
我讨厌一个人被留下
I hate being left alone.
一个人的时候  我就想做各种疯狂的事
When I'm alone, it makes me want to do all kinds of crazy things.
不该让女人跟你这种帅哥独处
No woman should be left alone with a man like you.
你想要我吗
Do you want me?
做一些我们不该做的事
To do something we shouldn't?
我不会说的
My lips are sealed.
后备箱里有我需要的东西
There's something I need in the trunk.
看好了
Bear withness.
洛德夫人  专家到了
Mrs. Lord, the specialist has arrived.
对她来说  洗澡永远不是目的
The bathing thing with her was never about bathing.
只是出戏  或者说是营销
It was always theater, or maybe it was retail.
货要先展示才好卖
You can't make a sale without showing the goods.
是麦卡锡
It's McCarthy.
希望你不介意我这么说
Do you mind if I say that
你比我想的要像个男人
you're twice the man I thought you were?
你是战士
You're a warrior,
杀手
a killer.
你就是我想要的男人
You're everything I want of a man
但我永远没法让你说实话
but I can never get the honesty out of you.
你原本可以是我需要的一切
You could've been eveything that I needed.
你现在依旧可以  你改头换面了
You still could be, you're a new man!
别忘了她做过的事  别忘了她的真面目
Remember what she did. Remember what she is.
等着你的出场
Wait for your opening.
等着盖尔做完她的事
Wait for Gail to do ber bit.
当你能对我免疫的时候  我会通知你的
When you're immune to me, I'll let you know.
请退后  夫人  让我杀了他
Step back, Mrs., let me kill him.
请
Please...
动手吧
...do.
六发子弹  没有一发入脑
Six shots, without a single head wound.
现在就看速度和运气了
And now it all gets down to speed and luck.
她的眼睛湿润  充满了爱
Her eyes are wet and full of love.
我从没想过
I never dream,
你就是我想要的一切
you're everything I ever wanted,
我需要的一切
everything I need...
你和我直到永远
...you and me, forever.
结束了
It's over.
疼痛让你解脱了
Pain has set you free.
你不再是好人了  德怀特
You're not good anymore, Dwight.
你更像我了
You're more like me.
跟我一样吧
Be like me.
忘了过去的德怀特吧
Let the old Dwight go.
忘了这张过去的面孔吧
Let it go, this old face.
她靠近我  我不得不看
She pulls close and I got to look.
而我只想
And all I wanted is to be lost
迷失在她的臂弯里
in the sight and sound and smell of her.
-我无法思考  -我们可以自由
- I can't think straight. - We can be free.
我们可以永远快乐地在一起
We can be happy, together, forever.
不
No...
她的吻仿佛是天堂
Her kiss is a promise of paradise.
-德怀特  -手中的枪响了
- Dwight... - The gun barks and balks in my hand.
随着一声叹息  生命离开了艾娃
Life leaves Ava, with a sigh.
警笛响起了  我们会从小路逃走
Sirens climbing the hill, we'll take the backroads,
旧时运私酒的路
the old bootlegged roads,
谁也抓不到我们
don't ever catch us,
我要回家了
I'm going home.
在罪恶之城的背街小巷走一圈
Walk down the back alley in Sin City,
什么都能找到
and you can find anything.
听说在这儿能找到一位克罗尼先生
I was told I could find a man here by the name of Mr. Kroenig.
你要称呼  克罗尼医生
That's a doctor, Kroenig, to you.
遵命
Yes, sir.
不管有没有执照
License or no license,
这双手仍然宝刀未老
these hands still got well, what it takes,
只要我做好准备
once I preped.
你有多少钱
How much you got?
你有40块  那就是40块的活儿
Forty bucks you got? Forty bucks worth you get!
稳如磐石
Steady as a rock...
只要我做好准备
...once I'm prepped.
40块帮你取出子弹
Forty bucks got you the bullet
但你的手  可有很多骨头需要护理
but that hands of yours, a lot of bones need help.
把鞋给我  我帮你治一个小时
I'll give you an hour, for your shoes.
拿去
Take them.
我尽力去想胜利  报仇
I did my best to think about winning, revenge.
那个老头肯定喜欢冰棍
The old man must have like popsicles,
拿来当夹板的木棍  他都要先舔舔
he uses the sticks for splints. He licks them first.
他娘的一句谢谢也不说
Not so much of a goddamn thank you.
好心有个屁用
Generosity don't count for shit.
这该死的时代
This dead age.
干得不错  罗克
Quite a job he did on me, Roark.
我连鞋都没了
Even my shoes.
没什么能被你夺走了
There's nothing more you can take,
除了
except...
玛茜  那个姑娘
Marcie, the girl.
天哪
Oh my Christ.
玛茜
Marcie.
玛茜  这与你无关
Oh, Marcie, you weren't a part of this.
我找你只是为了让他们放松警惕
You were just there to throw them off their game.
我把你扯进了什么
What have I dragged you into?
今夜变得如此漫长难熬
This has turned into one long, bad night.
窗户没锁
The windows are not locked.
不是个好兆头
Never a good sign.
至少在罪恶之城不是
Not in Sin City.
看看谁终于出现了
Look who has decided to show up?
给他露一手
Give the man a hand.
再给他露一手
Give the man another hand.
身败名裂  身无分文
Ruined, penniless,
无亲无故  无人惦记
friendless and forgotten.
你真的还不如死了  强尼
You really be better off dead, Johnny.
但我就喜欢你这个样子
But I like you just the way you're.
我太自大了
I got cocky.
我太自大了  结果害死了玛茜
I got cocky and I got Marcie dead.
该死  强尼
Damn it, Johnny.
等有时间了再自责
Hate yourself only when you got the time.
现在先想想今晚的赌局
Think about tonight's game.
那才是现在最重要的事
That's all it matters now.
你需要的只是钱
And all you need is money,
只要一块钱  就足够翻身了
just one lousy buck would be enough to get you started.
你好  女士
Hello, ma'am.
我没钱付账
I don't have the money to pay
但我能要杯水吗
but could I ask you for a glass of water?
可以
Yeah.
时运不济
Time is tough all over.
谢谢
Thank you.
手怎么了
What's with the hand?
玩牌的时候惹错了人
I beat the wrong guys at cards.
运气背
Tough break.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
你等一下
Just a second, you.
你没我讨厌的毛病
You don't stink of anything I don't like
还有点像我的前男友
and you kinda remind me of an old boyfriend, okay?
虽然帮不了你什么
This won't take you very far.
宝贝儿  这足够带我去月球了
Sweetheart, it's going to take me to the moon.
罪恶之城  一切皆有可能
Sin City, you never know.
别一口气花完
Don't spend it all in one place.
帅哥  你要那些钱干嘛
Hey, handsome, what are you gonna do with all that?
我要去杀了罗克
I'm going to kill Roark.
那个罗克可没那么容易死
That Roark there, don't die that easy.
说不定我会给你惊喜
I just might surprise you.
看起来你的幸运之手出事了  孩子
Looks like something happened to your game hand, son.
不跟
I fold.
怎么了  能人
What's wrong, hotshot?
上次的幸运女郎没来就不行了吗
No good without the lady luck you brought here last time?
我没事
I'll be fine.
-不跟  -不跟
- I'm done. - I'm out.
给我三张
I need three.
庄家要两张
Dealer takes two.
-过牌  -过牌
- Check. - Check.
我加一百
I bet a hundred.
该死
Shit!
不跟
Fold.
没有幸运之手就不一样了  是吧
Just not the same without your game hand, is it?
我两手皆可
I'm ambidextrous.
切牌
Cut.
过牌
Check.
五百
Five hundred.
我跟
I'm in.
我再加
I'll raise you...
五百
...five hundred more.
-不跟  -不跟
- I fold. - I'm done.
-这是你的五百块  -操
- Here is your five more, pretty boy. - Shit!
你喜欢你妈
You favored your mother,
她就是个婊子  还不太称职
she was a whore, not a very good one.
她是天使
She was an angel.
全押
I'm all in.
为了一切
For the works.
跟
Call.
四个A
Four aces.
看  跟你说了  我不会输
See, I told you, I never lose.
我打败你了
I beat you,
打败你两次  说明我比你强
twice, that means I'm better than you're
每个人都知道了
and everybody knows it
每次有人讲起这个故事  我都再打败你一次
'cause I beat you again every time somebody tells that story,
他们会说他们不会说  但他们会的
and they will all say they won't tell it but they will.
会有人不断地讲起这个故事
That's the story that will be told again and again
直到你死  直到你死后很多年
until you're dead and long after you're dead.
我永远打败你了
I beat you forever.
他们也都知道打败我会发生什么
And they all know what happens when you do.
向你妈问好
Say hello to your mama.
她一直是个蠢婊子
She always was a stupid bitch.
权力说什么就是什么
Power is what power does.
如果要我给年轻人建议
Say I give any young man advices,
无论何时何地都是这句
it'll be this where or whenever.
把那垃圾丢出去  咱们接着玩
Now take out that trash, let's get back to the game!
约翰·哈提根
我不能再次失去你了
I can't lose you, not again.
你从未失去我  南希
You never lose me, Nancy.
这些年  她一直在那儿
All this time, she, was right there.
在你玩牌的俱乐部里跳舞
Dancing in the club where you play poker.
得找机会
You gotta be looking for a chance
把她给做了  议员
to put this one thru' the ring, senator.
南希·卡拉汉
Nancy Callahan.
我儿子伊森就是因她而死
My son Ethen was killed because of her.
如今已经过去了四年
It has been 4 years now and still,
她还是会去哈提根的墓前献花
she's planting flowers at Hartigan's grave.
她似乎在向那个警察表示谢意
She's showing gratitude for the looks of it to the cop.
感谢那个
Gratitude to the cop,
把你儿子大卸八块的警察
who ripped your son to pieces.
哈提根把我儿子变成了一个怪物
Hartigan turned my son into a freak.
不  是成全他变成了怪物
No, complete him as a freak
但我不怪她
but I hardly blame the young lady for...
如此执念
...obsession.
不过是几分无用的哀悼罢了
It's nothing more than a little fluff sorrow.
可能没那么简单
It might not be that simple.
她不知如何拿到了哈提根的枪
Somehow she got her hands on Hartigan's old pistol.
她每晚开工前都会去射击场
She hits the ring every night just before work.
现在枪法很不错
She become quite a good shot.
你知道她把靶子想象成谁吧
And I can only imagine whose face she sees on that target.
接着说
I'm listening.
她上班时有时候好像疯了一样
She's acting kinda crazy sometimes, at work.
她还喝酒  最近几周才开始
She's drinking, just a little past few weeks.
她以前从不喝
She never drank before.
似乎  她在累积什么
It's all like, she's building up to something.
也许是在积累她的勇气
Maybe, building her...nerve.
可以了  警长
That will be all, lieutenant.
这小婊子简直要让我硬了
This little bitch is turning me on.
这里满是恶臭
This place stinks.
我以前从未注意
I never use to notice.
至少跳舞时没有
not when I dance.
现在我什么都能闻到
Now I smell everything.
什么都能看到
I see it all.
一件不落
Every damn thing.
我知道我的位置
I know exactly where I'm.
我知道我的身份
I know exactly what I'm.
我不再用脱衣舞娘的逻辑去思考了
I don't use that stripper's logic anymore,
不再觉得他们都是废物而我不是
that they're losers and I'm not.
当我可以冲他开枪时我意识到我死定了
It was when I could shoot at him that I realize I'm dead,
我不是个成竹在胸的女人
that I wasn't a woman with a plan.
我只是个醉鬼
I was just a drunk...
我满足他们的愿望
I give them what they want
然后转身离开
and I get the hell outta there.
你冲他开了枪
You shot him in the gut.
是意外
It was a mishap.
谁来负责
Who is to pay?
糜烂的都市  污染所有触碰它的人
...rotten town, it soots anybody who touches.
这座糜烂的都市  却无法腐蚀地下的土壤
it's a rotten town but it can't corrupt its soil.
那是有你的土壤  哈提根
It's soil to you, John Hartigan.
把酒瓶放下  南希  你喝的够多了
Put that bottle down, Nancy. You had enough.
他们逼你骗我  你现在根本不在这里
They made you lie to me, you're not even here right now.
-你说过你不会离开我  -我没有离开你
- You said you never leave me. - I never left you.
永远不会
I never would.
永远
Never.
你现在根本不在这里  你已经死了
You're not even here right now. You're dead!
你脑袋开花了
You blew your brains out.
你把枪塞进嘴里然后扣下了扳机
You stuck a gun in your mouth and you blew your brains out.
我有我的原因  没有其他的选择
I had my reasons, there was no way out.
我恨你
I hate you!
警察杀手自杀
-你发誓会永远爱我  -我会永远爱你
- You swore you'll always love me. - And I always will.
没人能猜到地狱是什么
No one has ever guessed what hell is.
是目睹你爱的人
It's watching the people you love...
痛苦不堪
...in pain.
你是我唯一爱过的人
You're the man I ever loved
却离我而去
and you left me alone.
你从不认为
You never thought I'd stand a chance
我能干掉罗克的儿子
with that goddamn son of Roark.
杀人如麻的凶手
你从不相信我
You didn't believe in me.
你不相信像我这样的小丑
You didn't think a little piece of arse like me
可以打败全州最有权势的人
could take down the most powerful man in the state.
杀人如麻的凶手
也许我会证明你们俩都错了
Maybe I'll prove both of you wrong.
也许我会发疯
Maybe I would go crazy.
-现在发疯挺好的  -我爱你  南希
- Crazy is sounding pretty good right now. - I love you, Nancy.
你个小婊子  我会让你尖叫至死
You little slut! You gonna scream before you die.
你疯了
You're out of your mind...
我欣赏你的执着  但你什么都没有
I appreciate the obsession but you got nothing...
你要是有胆子  都能杀我50次了
You could've killed me 50 times if you've the nerve,
可你没有
but you don't.
你什么也不是
You're nothing...
你会尖叫的  就像我儿子想要的
You'll scream, just like my boy wanted you to...
宝贝儿  你去哪儿了
Darling, where have you been
你把你的一头秀发怎么了
and what have you done to your beautiful hair?
别担心  那些混蛋会得到他们想要的
Don't worry, those bastards are getting what they want.
他们总会得到他们想要的
They always get what they want.
简直太棒了  是吧  你怎么了
This is great, isn't it? What's up with you?
有什么不对劲  我要走了
Something's wrong, I'm out of here.
简直像眼看着我妹妹自甘堕落
Oh, watching my sister getting nasty,
我去散散步
I'm taking a hike.
准备
Ready.
你很美  南希
You are beautiful, Nancy.
别这样对自己
Don't do this to yourself.
美  美  美
Pretty, pretty, pretty...
如果有男人这么对你  我一定撕了他
If a man did this to you, I'll tear him to pieces.
哈提根警长  你给了我灵感
Lieutenant Hartigan, you just gave me a great idea.
别这样  宝贝
No, babe.
南希
Nancy...
说名字就行
Just give me a damn name.
罗克
Roark.
要对抗很多人  咱们需要工具
Up against a lot, we need tools.
好像是麻烦
Looks like trouble.
好像是乐子
Looks like Christmas.
-你们错过了最后一轮啊  -少废话
- Well, you missed last call, boys. - Bullshit!
我们是来打劫的  混蛋
We're ripping this place, arse hole.
不滚就死
Move or die!
希望你不介意我这么说
I hope you don't mind me saying this, but...
你真性感
you look hot.
没必要留活口
There's no reason to leave anybody alive.
没人是无辜的  而且不能留下证人
Nobody's innocent. We can't leave anybody able to talk.
别心软  一个活口不留
Don't go soft on me, kid. Don't leave anybody breathing.
我会的  我在外面转一圈  干掉保安
I won't. I'll work the perimeter and nail the guards.
宝贝  你真有天赋  我去里面
Baby, you're a natural. I'll work the inside.
我怎么知道你进去了
How would I know when you're in?
你会知道的
You'll have a pretty good idea.
该死的冲我开枪了
Damn thing has fired on me.
几乎全搞定了
I nearly got them all but
但这个混蛋冒出来了
this piece of shit over here, he came up on me.
该死的  我想就到这儿了
This piece of crap... I think I'll stuck.
给
Here.
坐吧
Take a seat.
你真好
You're a peach.
我来就行
I got this.
你这个聪明的小婊子
You clever, clever little whore.
你居然能走到这么远
I can't believe you made it this far.
你的哈提根把我儿子的命根子断了
Your Hartigan blew my son's pecker off.
我接下来应该冲哪里开枪呢
So...where shall I shoot you next?
你紧致的小蛮腰
The tight little belly of yours?
我拿枪对着你呢  小姐
I'm holding a gun on you, young lady.
规矩是你要求饶  以为我也许不会开枪
The rules are, you pretend there's a chance that I won't shoot you.
我说过的  你会尖叫至死
I told you, you would scream before you die.
这是我欠我儿子的
I owe it to my son.
说实话  只告诉你
Frankly, between you and me,
我还是接受了伊森不是当总统的料
I finally accepted that...Ethen is not...presidential material.
在精神病院拉选票真是太难了
I had a hard time buying him an election in the same asylum,
但他终究是我儿子
but he was my son, honey.
我的儿子
He was my son.
现在  他要听你尖叫了
And now, he's going to hear you scream.
尖叫吧
Scream...
这是为了约翰·哈提根  混蛋
This is for John Hartigan, fucker!
这靡烂的都市腐蚀了每一个人
This rotten town has soiled everybody...